CHRISTOPHER "CJ" JOHNSON

UX/UI Designer

CONTACT

Johnsonce3101@gmail.com

Knoxville, TN

in My Profile

My Portfolio

SKILLS

Wireframes

Design Psychology

Figma Web Development

Prototyping

User Research

Data Synthesis

Sketching

Usability Testing

Journey Mapping **UI** Design

Adobe Creative

Front End -

HTML

CSS

JavaScript (JS)

Node.js

Git

Bootstrap

Design systems

Accessibility

EDUCATION

Human Computer Interaction for UX (Cert.)

MIT

UX/UI Design (Cert.)

V School

Web Development (Cert.)

DigitalCrafts

Intelligence & Technology (A.A.S)

Community College of the Air-force

Psychology (B.A.)

(Clinical)

East Tennessee State University

PROFILE

Hi, a bit about me I'm a passionate professional who balances combining elements of psychology, and design thinking to create products that fulfill user needs. A capable team player with an equal ability to take initiative and lead in order to get the job done. A UX Researcher exploring user needs, pain points, and behaviors.

EXPERIENCE

Application Development Analyst

Accenture (10/2021 - 10/2022)

- · Designed software applications for various operating systems according to business & client requirements
- · Developed RICEFW solutions for client stakeholders using agile methodologies.
 - Provided timely data analysis for 10k+ defects to improve productivity
 - · Decreased time spent on bugs/defects
- · Certified in Salesforce (SF) Platform (Vlocity OmniStudio Developer & Consultant).

Brand Strategist

NueWay Studios (08/2019 - 04/2020)

- · First point of contact for clients, guided clients through initial on boarding processes and branded marketing strategies
- · Designed UX for digital contract signing process
- · Elevated customer experience engagement strategy
 - · Designed presentation/contract sign room using visual, auditory,
 - · lead to 50% contract signing increase.

All-Source Intelligence Technician

U.S. Air-Force (07/2015 - 07/2019)

- · Designed first ever non-kinetic targeting product (digital) in a crossfunctional environment.
- · Assessed vulnerabilities of DoD cyberspace enterprise that could be exploited by adversaries.
- Reduced product completion from 3 months to 48 days.
- Conducted database research prepared intelligence reports and charts.
- Supervision
 - Team lead: Trained supervisors and co-worker on critical thinking, analytical writing skills, and presentation.
 - · Trained team members of the importance of resilience.
 - Emphasized organization of documentation regarding product research.